Guide to the W. Keith Kennedy papers, 1971-1978.
Kennedy, W. Keith papers, 1971-1978.
- SUNY--Provost for Graduate Education and Research (Murray), 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 48)
- SUNY--Provost for Lifelong Learning, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 49)
- SUNY--Vice Chancellor for Academic Programs (Dearing, B.), 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 50)
- SUNY--Vice Chancellor for Campus Development, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 51)
- SUNY--Executive Vice Chancellor (Kelly), 1974 (Box 24, Folder 52)
- SUNY--Vice Chancellor for Faculty and Staff Relations (Komisar), 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 53)
- SUNY--Vice Chancellor for Finance, Management, and Business (Spindler), 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 54)
- SUNY--Vice Chancellor for Personnel and Employee Relations, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 55)
- SUNY--Vice Chancellor University Affairs, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 56)
- SUNY--Vice Chancellor for University-Wide Services and Special Programs, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 57)
- SUNY at Albany, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 58)
- SUNY at Buffalo, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 59)
- SUNY--Geneseo, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 60)
- Mohawk Valley Community College, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 61)
- SUNY--Potsdam, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 62)
- Schenectady Community College, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 63)
- Agricultural and Technical Colleges, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 64)
- Agricultural and Technical College at Farmingdale, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 65)
- Agricultural and Technical Colleges (ATC) Presidents' Meeting, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 66)
- Circular Letter (Kennedy, W. K.), 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 67)
- Circular Letters (Kent, G. C.), 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 68)
- Circular Letters (Spencer, J. W.), 1973-1975 (Box 24, Folder 69)
- Assistant to the Dean (Kennedy, Laing), 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 70)
- Assistant Dean Position, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 71)
- Associate Dean (Spencer, J. W.), 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 72)
- Coordinator of Planning--Agriculture and Life Sciences (Kent, G. C.), 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 73)
- Agriculture and Life Sciences Dean Search Committee, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 74)
- Palm, Charles E. (Liberty Hyde Bailey Professor of Agricultural Sciences), 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 75-76)
- Agricultural Economics, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 1-3)
- Agricultural Economics--Bulletins, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Earle, Wendell G.Testimonial Dinner, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Agricultural Engineering, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 6-7)
- Agronomy, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 8-9)
- Animal Science, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 10-12)
- Bailey Hortorium, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Communication Arts, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Media Services, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Ward, Professor William B., 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Department of Communication Arts--Annual Report, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Education, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Entomology, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 19-21)
- Extension, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 22-24)
- Ozbun, Jim L., 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 25)
- County Agents, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 26)
- 4-H, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 27)
- Finance and Business Office, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 28)
- Food Science, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 29-30)
- Floriculture, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 31)
- Floriculture--Headship, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 32)
- Geneva, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 33-35)
- Institute of Food Science, 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 36)
- International Agriculture Development (IAD), 1974-1975 (Box 25, Folder 37-39)
- Landscape Architecture, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Long Island Ornamentals Research Laboratory, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Microbiology, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Mann Library, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Natural Resources, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 5-7)
- Moen, Aaron N., 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Plant Breeding, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Biometrics Unit, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Plant Breeding Chairmanship, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Plant Pathology, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- Pomology, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Poultry, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Research, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 15-16)
- Resident Instruction, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 17-18)
- Rural Sociology, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 19)
- Long Island Vegetable Research Laboratory, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 20)
- Sweet, R. D., 1975 (Box 26, Folder 21)
- Vegetable Crops, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 22)
- Biological Sciences (O'Brien, R. D.), 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 23-24)
- Biological Sciences--Accessory Instruction, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Biological Sciences--Executive Committee Meetings, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 26)
- Biochemistry, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 27)
- Ecology, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 28)
- Genetics, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 29)
- Neurobiology, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 30)
- Wiegand Herbarium, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 31)
- Correspondence--A, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 32)
- Office of Academic Funding, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 33)
- Accessory Instruction, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 34)
- Admissions Office--Cornell University, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 35)
- Adviser's (Kennedy), 1975 (Box 26, Folder 36)
- Affirmative Action, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 37)
- Agribusiness Council, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 38)
- Agricultural Council of America, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 39)
- Agricultural Leaders' Forum, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 40)
- Agricultural Resource Commission, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 41)
- Agricultural Stabilization and Conservation Service (ASCS), 1974 (Box 26, Folder 42)
- Agriculture and Life Sciences Fund, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 43)
- Agriculture and Life Sciences Fund Advisory Council, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 44)
- Agriculture and Life Sciences Fund Advisory Committee, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 45)
- New York State Department of Agriculture and Markets, 1973-1975 (Box 26, Folder 46)
- Agway, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 47)
- Secretary of Agriculture, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 48)
- Allocations to Departments and Sections, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 49)
- Alpha Gamma Sigma, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 50)
- Alumni Association--Agriculture and Life Sciences, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 51)
- Alumni--Cornell, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 52)
- American Agriculturist, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 53)
- Aquaculture, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 54)
- College of Architecture, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 55)
- College of Arts and Sciences, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 56)
- New York State Atomic and Space Development Authority, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 57)
- Correspondence--B, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 58)
- Beef Cattle, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 59)
- Black Agriculturalists, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 60)
- Brandy, N. C., 1974 (Box 26, Folder 61)
- Breakabean, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 62)
- Buildings and Properties, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 63)
- Division of Budget, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 64)
- Correspondence--C, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 65)
- Catskills, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 66)
- Center for Environmental Quality Management (CEQM), 1973-1975 (Box 26, Folder 67)
- CEQM Governing Board, 1973-1975 (Box 26, Folder 68-70)
- CEQM, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 71)
- Computer Services, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 72)
- Conference Office, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 73)
- Cor-Ag Symposium, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 74)
- Cornell Plantations, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 75)
- COSEP, 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 76)
- Correspondence--D, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Dairylea, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Dairy Prices, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 3-4)
- Dean's College Account, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Dean's List, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- University Development, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Dyson, John S., 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Correspondence--E, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Eastern Milk Cooperative, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- East-West Center, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Education Department, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Empire Farm Days, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- Empire State Potato Club, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Empire State Soil Fertility Association, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 15)
- Endowed Accounting, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- Endowed--Budget, 1973-1975 (Box 27, Folder 17)
- Energy, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- Energy Forum, 1974-1974 (Box 27, Folder 19)
- Energy, Agriculture, and Waste Management Conference, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 20)
- College of Engineering, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 21)
- Department of Environmental Conservation, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 22)
- Environmental Leaders' Forum, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 23)
- Environmental Studies Program, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 24)
- Educational Opportunity Program (EOP), 1974 (Box 27, Folder 25)
- Correspondence--F, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 26)
- "Facts and Figures" (Publication), 1975 (Box 27, Folder 27)
- Faculty Grants, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 28)
- Farm Credit Banks, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 29)
- Farm Foundation, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 30)
- Conference Board of Farm Organizations, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 31)
- Federal Research and Development Program, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 32)
- Financial Systems Development (Ostrom, J. S.), 1974 (Box 27, Folder 33)
- New York State Food Conference, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 34)
- Ford Foundation, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 35)
- Funnel--College of Agriculture and Life Sciences Income, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 36)
- Correspondence--G, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 37)
- General Services, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 38)
- Local Government--Program, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 39)
- Graduate School, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 40)
- Grade Distribution Percentages, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 41)
- Correspondence--H, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 42)
- Department of Health, Education, and Welfare, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 43)
- Higher Education, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 44)
- Ho-Nun-De-Kah, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 45)
- Hotel School, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 46)
- Hudson Valley Lab, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 47)
- Hudson Basin Project--Water Resources, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 48)
- Hudson Basin Project--Transportation, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 49)
- Hudson Basin Project--Leisure Time and Recreation, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 50)
- Human Affairs Program, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 51)
- College of Human Ecology, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 52)
- Correspondence--I, 1973-1975 (Box 27, Folder 53)
- Indirect Costs, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 54)
- Industrial and Labor Relations, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 55)
- Inflation and Higher Education, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 56)
- Information Kits, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 57)
- International Student Office, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 58)
- Center of International Studies, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 59-60)
- Isles of Shoals, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 61)
- Correspondence--J, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 62)
- John Wendell Anderson Professorship, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 63)
- Correspondence--K, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 64)
- Correspondence--L, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 65)
- Land Use Inventory, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 66)
- Law School, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 67)
- Libraries, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 68)
- Lilly Endowment, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 69)
- Local Government Program, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 70)
- Members of Assembly, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 71)
- Members of Congress, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 72)
- Governor's Office, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 73)
- Governor's Task Force, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 74)
- Legislative Leaders, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 75)
- Material Mailed to Legislative Leaders, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 76-77)
- New York State Office for Local Government, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 78)
- Senators, 1974-1975 (Box 27, Folder 79)
- Senate Finance Committee, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 80)
- United States Ways and Means Committee, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 81)
- Correspondence--M, 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Lincoln University of Missouri, 1973-1974 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Management Systems and Analysis, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Master Plan, 1974-1974 (Box 28, Folder 4-5)
- Medical College--Cornell University and Upstate Medical, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Miner Institute, 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Miner-Cornell Cooperative Programs Review Meeting, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Model Farm Report, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Mote Marine Laboratory, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Correspondence--N, 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- National Science Foundation, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- News Releases, 1973-1974 (Box 28, Folder 13)
- National Canners Association, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- New York Farm Bureau, 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 15-16)
- New York Farmers, 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 17)
- New York's Food and Life Sciences Quarterly, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 18)
- New York State Agricultural Society, 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 19)
- New York State Council of Agricultural Organizations, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 20)
- New York State Council of Farmer Cooperatives, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 21)
- New York State Farm Electrification Council, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 22)
- New York State Fish and Wildlife Management Board, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 23)
- New York State Flower Industries, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 24)
- New York State Forest Practice Board, 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 25)
- New York State Grange, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 26)
- New York State Nurserymen, 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 27)
- New York State Seed Association, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 28)
- Northeast Regional Center for Rural Development, 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 29-30)
- Nutrition--Budget, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 31)
- Nutritional Studies, 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 32-33)
- Nutrition Newsletter, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 34)
- Graduate School of Nutrition, 1973-1974 (Box 28, Folder 35)
- Division of Nutritional Sciences (Campbell, Dr. T. Collin. T., 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 36)
- Correspondence--O, 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 37)
- Occupational Education--Report, 1973-1974 (Box 28, Folder 38)
- Ombudsman, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 39)
- Operation Hitchhike, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 40)
- Overhead, 1973-1974 (Box 28, Folder 41)
- Ornithological Laboratory, 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 42)
- Correspondence--P, 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 43)
- Personnel, 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 44)
- Pesticides and Chemicals, 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 45)
- University of the Philippines, 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 46)
- Pinchot Institute, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 47)
- Director of Planning and Development, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 48)
- Plant Science--Associate Director of Plant Science and Research Contacts, 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 49)
- Potato Growers, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 50)
- Policy Studies, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 51)
- Presidential Appointments, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 52)
- Priorities Study (Macneil, Ian R.), 1975 (Box 28, Folder 53)
- Professor-at-Large (Boulding, Kenneth), 1974 (Box 28, Folder 54)
- Professor-at-Large Selection Committee, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 55)
- Correspondence--R, 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 56)
- Recycling, 1973-1975 (Box 28, Folder 57)
- Office of Registrar, 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 58)
- Retiring Faculty, 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 59)
- Rockefeller Foundation, 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 60)
- Rootstocks, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 61)
- ROTC, 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 62)
- Rural Development Act (Title V), 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 63)
- Rural Development--Chenango County, 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 64-65)
- Rural Development--Clinton County, 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 66-69)
- Rural Development--Wyoming County, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 70)
- Russians, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 71)
- Correspondence--S, 1974-1975 (Box 28, Folder 72)
- Sabbatical Summaries, 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Salaries, 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Salaries, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Scholar Incentive, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Scholarships, 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Science, Technology, and Society, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Sea Grant, 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 7-8)
- Sea Grant Governing Board, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Sea Grant Newspapers, 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Sea Grant Site Visit, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- Sea Grant Annual Report, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- Sea Grant Annual Report for Year I, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 13)
- Sea Grant Program, 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 14)
- Sea Grant Governing Board Meeting, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 15)
- Sea Grant Proposal for Institutional Support (Volume I), 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 16)
- Sea Grant Proposal for Institutional Support (Volume II), 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 17)
- Service Recognition, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 18)
- Sexual Discrimination, HEW Rules, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 19)
- Social Sciences, 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 20)
- Soil Conservation Service, 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 21)
- Statler, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 22)
- Steward, F. C., 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 23)
- Dean of Students, 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 24)
- Office of Student Records and Finance, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 25)
- Study of Academic Support Service, 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 26)
- Correspondence--T, 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 27)
- Tennessee Valley Authority (TVA), 1975 (Box 29, Folder 28)
- Training Grants, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 29)
- Transfer of Funds, 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 30)
- Tuition Assistance Program (TAP), 1974 (Box 29, Folder 31)
- Tuition, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 32)
- Television, 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 33)
- Correspondence--U, 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 34)
- Uihlein Farm, 1974-1976 (Box 29, Folder 35)
- Cornell University Council, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 36)
- Cornell University Press, 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 37)
- University Relations, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 38)
- University Senate, 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 39)
- Center for Urban Development Research, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 40)
- USDA, 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 41)
- United States Fish and Wildlife Service, 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 42)
- United States Plant, Soil, and Nutrition Laboratory, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 43)
- Correspondence--V, 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 44)
- Veterinary College, 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 45)
- Correspondence--W, 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 46)
- Water Resources and Marine Sciences Center, 1974-1975 (Box 29, Folder 47)
- Wine, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 48)
- Wayne County Migrant Project, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 49)
- Work Week, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 50)
- Work Group on World Food Problems, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 51)
- World Food Conference, Meeting of Non-Government Organizations, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 52)
- World Food Forum, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 53)
- World Food Situation, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 54)
- Correspondence--A, 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 55)
- Office of Academic Funding, 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 56)
- Adams, Mort, 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 57)
- Dean of Admissions and Financial Aid, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 58)
- Affirmative Action, 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 59)
- Africana Studies and Research Center, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 60)
- Council of Agricultural Organizations (Empire State), 1974-1976 (Box 29, Folder 61)
- Agricultural Production, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 62)
- Agriculture Circle, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 63)
- Agriculture and Life Science Fund, 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 64)
- Department of Agriculture and Markets, 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 65-66)
- Agricultural Leaders' Forum, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 67)
- Agricultural Resource Commission, 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 68)
- Agriculture Positive Action Council (AgPAC), 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 69)
- Agway, 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 70)
- Alumni Association--Agriculture and Life Sciences, 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 71)
- Alumni Office, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 72)
- American Agriculturist, 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 73)
- American Council on Education, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 74)
- College of Architecture, 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 75)
- College of Arts and Sciences, 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 76)
- Correspondence--B, 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 77)
- Bank--Farm Credit Banks of Springfield, 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 78)
- Benefits of Agricultural Research, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 79)
- Black Bio-Medical, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 80)
- Black River-St. Lawrence Resource Conservation and Development Project. Lawrence Resource Conservation, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 81)
- Bloodmobile, 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 82)
- Brandy, N. C., 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 83)
- Division of Budget, 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 84)
- Buildings and Properties, 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 85)
- Building Security, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 86)
- Bursar, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 87)
- School of Business and Public Administration, 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 88)
- Correspondence--C, 1975-1976 (Box 29, Folder 89)
- Calendar of Administrative Expectations of Departments, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Career Development Program, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Carnegie Corporation, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Catskills, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Center for Environmental Quality Management (CEQM), 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- CEQM Governing Board, 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Chancellor's Award, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Chairmen Concerns and Special Funding Requests Conference, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- American Chemical Society (Large, Dr. Robert. Robert;), 1976 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Colman, Gould, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Commissioner of Commerce, 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- Community Forum, Agriculture and Life Sciences, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 12)
- Community Research and Training Institute at Cornell University (CRTI), 1976 (Box 30, Folder 13)
- Computer Services, 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 14)
- Conferences, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 15)
- Cornell Plantations, 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 16)
- Cornell--State Relations, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 17)
- Committee on Special Educational Projects (COSEP), 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 18-19)
- University Counseling/Advising Network, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 20)
- Correspondence--D, 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 21)
- Dairylea, 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 22)
- Dairy Herd Improvement, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 23)
- Dairy Hearings, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 24)
- Dairy Industry Study Commission, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 25)
- Dean's List, 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 26)
- Delinquents, 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 27)
- Office of University Development, 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 28)
- Dairy Herd Improvement (DHI), 1975 (Box 30, Folder 29)
- Correspondence--E, 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 30)
- Economic Education Center, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 31)
- New York State Department of Education, 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 32)
- Efficiency of Agricultural Production in the Northeast, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 33)
- Empire Farm Days, 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 34)
- Empire State Potato Club, 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 35)
- Empire State Soil Fertility, 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 36)
- Energy, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 37)
- College of Engineering, 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 38)
- Enrollment Reductions, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 39)
- Department of Environmental Conservation, 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 40)
- Environmental Leaders' Forum (Fifth), 1976 (Box 30, Folder 41)
- Environmental Studies Program, 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 42-43)
- Correspondence--F, 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 44)
- How Farm Families Make Decisions, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 45)
- Fellowships, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 46)
- Fleet Garage, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 47)
- Office of Financial Aid, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 48)
- Financial Systems Development, 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 49)
- Food and Life Sciences Quarterly, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 50)
- Fredonia Lab, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 51)
- Freeze, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 52)
- Correspondence--G, 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 53)
- General Foods, 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 54)
- Gift File, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 55)
- Graduate School, 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 56)
- Graduate Students, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 57)
- Correspondence--H, 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 58)
- Hayes Classification, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 59)
- Department of Health, Education, and Welfare, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 60)
- University Health Services, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 61)
- Hearing for Assembly Task Force on Food and Farm Policy--Syracuse, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 62)
- Higher Education, 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 63)
- Ho-Nun-De-Kah, 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 64)
- New York State Horticultural Society, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 65)
- Hotel School, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 66)
- Hudson Basin Project, 1975-1976 (Box 30, Folder 67-69)
- Hudson Basin Project, 1974-1975 (Box 30, Folder 70-73)
- Hudson Basin Project, 1973-1974 (Box 30, Folder 74-76)